Guide to the Collection of musical autographs,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Scores
  - Humperdinck, Englebert "Hansel and Gretel" Fantasie. Score and parts., Schott's Sohne: Mainz, c. 1895, (59 pages bd., 39 parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 184)
  - Humperdinck, Englebert "Konigskinder." Parts., Max Brockhaus: Germany, c. 1897, (63 parts) (Box 23, Folder 185)
  - Jensen, Adolf "Hochzeitmusik." Parts., New York, [n.d.], (38 parts) (Box 23, Folder 186)
  - Kistler, C. Bayreuth Festival March. Op. 41. Orchestra score., [n.d.], (17 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy) (Box 23, Folder 187)
    [In copyist's hand. Ornate lettering on cover.]
  - Lalo "Rhapsodie." Score and parts., (50 parts ) (Box 23, Folder 188)
    [With pencil changes.]
  - Beethoven Symphony No. 1. Cello., [n.d.], (1 part) (Box 24, Folder 189)
    [With pencil changes and cover. ]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 6. Op. 68, Tams Music Library: New York; Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.]; 1893, (101 parts) (Box 24, Folder 190)
  - Bolzoni, G. "La Poule." Parts., [n.d.], (23 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 24, Folder 191)
  - Brahms, Johannes "Akademische," Fest Overture. Scores., Simrock: Berlin, (71 pages bd., 71 pages bd., 71 pages bd.) (Box 24, Folder 192)
  - Brahms, Johannes "Akademische," Fest Overture. Parts., Simrock: Berlin; Tams: New York, [n.d.], (5 parts a.ms. fair copy, 86 parts) (Box 24, Folder 193)
  - Dvorak, Anton "Slavic Dances 1-4," Op. 46. Parts., Tam's Music Library: New York, [n.d.], (68 parts) (Box 24, Folder 194)
  - Mozart, W.A. Larghesso. Score and parts with deteriorating covers., [n.d.], (4 pages a.ms. fair copy, 4 pages a.ms. fair copy, 8 pages) (Box 24, Folder 195)
    [Covers have script on the front.]
  - Lalo "Divertissment." Parts., Leipzig, [n.d.], (25 parts, 15 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 25, Folder 196)
  - Lalo Scherzo. Score and parts., Durand, Schoenework & Co.: Paris, [n.d.], (57 parts) (Box 25, Folder 197)
  - Lalo Allegro Appassionata. Parts., Berlin, [n.d.], (34 parts, 5 parts a.ms.) (Box 25, Folder 198)
  - Langey, Otto "Das Gespenst." Op. 51. Parts., [n.d.], (32 parts, 1 part a.ms.) (Box 25, Folder 199)
  - Langey, Otto "Lover and the Nightengale." Op. 49. Parts., Hanover, [n.d.], (35 parts) (Box 25, Folder 200)
  - Langey, Otto "Schottische Tanze: Two Scottish Dances." Score and parts., Carl Simon: Berlin, 1881, (47 pages bd., 48 parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 25, Folder 201)
  - Leoncavallo, R. "Pagliacci Prologue." Parts., Furstner: Berlin, 1892, (35 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 25, Folder 202)
  - Leoncavallo, R. "Gavotte" from the opera "Pagliacci." Score and parts for orchestra., Ascherberg & Co.: Leipzig, 1893, (7 pages bd., 21 parts, 4 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 25, Folder 203)
  - Leoncavallo, R. Pagliacci Minuet and Serenade. Score and parts., Ascherberg & Co.: Leipzig, 1893, (11 pages bd., 18 parts, 5 parts a.ms.) (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - Liszt, Franz "Hungarian Dances." Parts., Schlesinger: Berlin, [n.d.], (32 parts) (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - Liszt, Franz "Hungarian Rhapsody." Parts., Schuberth & Co.: New York, [n.d.], (42 parts, 1 part a.ms.s.) (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - Liszt, Franz "Hungarian Rhapsody." Score and parts., Schubert & Co.: New York, [n.d.], (24, pages bd. 32, parts ) (Box 25, Folder 207)
  - Liszt, Franz Faust Symphony. Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, [n.d.], (92 parts) (Box 25, Folder 208)
  - Liszt, Franz "Dante Symphony." Parts., [n.d.], (59 parts) (Box 25, Folder 209)
  - Liszt, Franz Hungarian Rhapsody No. 14. Score and parts., Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, (52 pages bd., 41 parts, 1 part a.ms.) (Box 25, Folder 210)
  - Liszt, Franz "Rakoczy March." Parts, J. Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, [n.d.], (42 parts) (Box 25, Folder 211)
  - Liszt, Franz "Kreugritter March." Parts., (41 parts, 4 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - Liszt, Franz "Gaudeamus igitur." Score and parts., J. Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, (42 pages bd., 35 parts) (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - Liszt, Franz "Nachtliche Zug." Parts., [n.d.], (45 parts a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - Liszt, Franz "Angelus." Score and parts., Schott's: Sohne, (9 pages bd., 18 parts) (Box 26, Folder 215)
  - Liszt, Franz Beethoven Cantata. Parts., [n.d.], (40 parts) (Box 26, Folder 216)
  - Liszt, Franz "Le Triomphe Funebre du Tasse." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (47 parts) (Box 26, Folder 217)
  - Liszt, Franz "Mephisto's Waltz." Parts., (47 parts a.ms.s.) (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - Liszt, Franz "Symphonilche Dictungen." Scores and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Hanover, (98 pages bd., 34 pages bd., 43 parts) (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - Liszt, Franz "Mazeppa." Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, (50 parts) (Box 26, Folder 220)
  - Liszt, Franz "Orpheus." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (52 parts, 2 parts) (Box 26, Folder 221)
  - Liszt, Franz "Promethee." Score and parts., Brietkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (43 parts) (Box 26, Folder 222)
  - Liszt, Franz First Hungarian Rhapsody. Score and parts., Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, [n.d.], (62 pages bd., 48 parts ) (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - Liszt, Franz Third Hungarian Rhapsody. Score and parts., Schuberth & Co.: New York, [n.d.], (36 pages bd., 43 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 26, Folder 224)
  - Massenet Overture "Le Cid." Score and parts., [n.d.], (34 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - Massenet "Valse: Roi de Lahore." Parts., [n.d.], (15 parts) (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Massenet Menuet de Manon. Score and parts., Hartmann: Paris, [n.d.], (7 pages bd., 16 parts) (Box 27, Folder 227)
  - Massenet Nocturne "La Navarraise." Parts., [n.d.], (21 parts, 1 part a.ms.s. fair copy) (Box 27, Folder 228)
  - Massenet Phaedre Overture. Parts., Schott's: Sohne, [n.d.], (27 parts) (Box 27, Folder 229)
  - Massenet "Rhapsodie Mauresque." Parts., [n.d.], (32 parts) (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - Massenet "Scenes Napolitaines." Parts., (36 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 27, Folder 231)
  - Massenet Suite Esclarmonde. Parts., [n.d.], (39 parts, 11 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Massenet "Marche Heroique." Score and parts., Hartmann: Paris, [n.d.], (46 pages bd.) (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Massenet. "Marche Le Cid." Parts., [n.d.], (35 parts) (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Massenet "Divertissement." Parts., Hartmann: Paris, [n.d.], (33 parts) (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Massenet "Le Cid," arranged by Aragonaise. Parts., Carl Fischer: New York, 1900 c., (20 parts) (Box 27, Folder 236)
  - Massenet "Le Cid" Ballet Music. Parts., (7 parts a.ms.s. fair copy, 37 parts) (Box 27, Folder 237)
    [In copyist's hand. With notes in pencil. Housed in two folders.]
  - Massenet "Le Roman d'Arlequin." Parts., Hartmann: Paris, [n.d.], (12 parts, 1 part photocopy) (Box 27, Folder 238)
  - Marsaniello "Guarache." Parts., [n.d.], (21 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 27, Folder 239)
  - Liszt, Franz "Hungarian Sturm Marsch." Parts., Schlesinger: Berlin, [n.d.], (45 parts) (Box 27, Folder 240)
  - Lizst, Franz "Die Vogelpredigt des heiligen Franz von Assisi." Parts., Stich und Druck: Leipzig, [n.d.], (39 parts) (Box 27, Folder 241)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix "Die Hebriden" Overture. Parts., New York, 20 May 1893, (32 parts) (Box 28, Folder 242)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Melusine Overture. Parts., [n.d.], (32 parts, 2 parts a.ms.s.) (Box 28, Folder 243)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Athalia Overture. Parts., Breitkopf and Hartl, [n.d.], (38 parts) (Box 28, Folder 244)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Overture to Heimkehr. Parts., (26 parts, 5 parts a.ms.s.) (Box 28, Folder 245)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Hochzut des Camacho Overture. Parts., (32 parts) (Box 28, Folder 246)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Symphony No. 5, "Reformation." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (49 parts, 5 parts a.ms.s.) (Box 28, Folder 247)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Loreley: Finale. Parts., [n.d.], (23 parts a.ms.) (Box 28, Folder 248)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Symphony No. 3. Parts., [n.d.], (44 parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 28, Folder 249)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Overture to Paulus. Parts., [n.d.], (33 parts) (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Lobgesang Symphony, Op. 52. Parts., [n.d.], (40 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 28, Folder 251)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Meerestille. Parts., [n.d.], (33 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 28, Folder 252)
  - Massenet Fairy Scenes. Parts., [n.d.], (39 parts, 2 parts a.ms.) (Box 28, Folder 253)
  - Massenet "Ein Sommernachtstraum" Overture. Parts., (30 parts, 2 parts a.ms.) (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Midsummer Night's Dream. op. 61. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (1 score, 43 parts) (Box 29, Folder 255)
    [Housed in three folders.]
  - Mendelssohn, Felix Symphony No. 4 in A Major. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (30 parts) (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - Meyer-Helmund, Erik Blissful Dream, op. 95. Score and parts., Schirmer: New York, [n.d.], (11 pages bd., 29 parts) (Box 29, Folder 257)
  - Meyerbeer, G. Der Nordstsern Overture. Parts., Berlin: Schlesinger, 15 May 1846, (39 parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy, 1 printed cover) (Box 29, Folder 258)
  - Meyerbeer, G. Le Prophet Ballet. Parts., [n.d.], (36 parts) (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - Meyerbeer, G. "Marche aux Flambeaux." Parts., [n.d.], (27 parts, 4 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 29, Folder 260)
  - Meyerbeer, G. "Struense" Overture. Score and parts., Berlin: Schlesinger, [n.d.], (60 pages bd., 39 parts) (Box 29, Folder 261)
  - Meyerbeer, G. First March. Parts., Schlesinger: Berlin, [n.d.], (45 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 29, Folder 262)
  - Meyerbeer, G. "Grosse Polonaise." Score and parts., Schlesinger: Berlin, [n.d.], (143 pages bd., 33 parts) (Box 29, Folder 263)
  - Meyerbeer, G. Dinorah Overture. Parts., [n.d.], (41 parts) (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Meyerbeer, G. Struense Overture. Score and parts., Schlesinger: Berlin, [n.d.], (60 pages bd., 25 parts, 9 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - Meyerbeer, G. "Huguenots" Overture. Parts., [n.d.], (27 parts a.ms. fair copy, 1 cover) (Box 30, Folder 266)
    [Handwritten script on the cover.]
  - Mozart "Don Juan Finale." Parts., [n.d.], (33 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 267)
  - Mozart "La Villanella rapita" Overture. Parts., Oertl: Hannover, [n.d.], (28 parts) (Box 30, Folder 268)
  - Mozart Zauberflote Overture. Score and parts., Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (26 pages bd. 29 parts, 3 parts a.ms.s. ) (Box 30, Folder 269)
  - Mozart Symphony K. 425, C major. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (26 parts) (Box 30, Folder 270)
  - Mozart Symphony No. 39. Parts., [n.d.], (43 parts) (Box 30, Folder 271)
  - Mozart Idomeneus Overture. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig and Simrock: Bonn, [n.d.], (30 parts, 6 a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 272)
  - Mozart Don Giovanni Overture. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (34 parts) (Box 30, Folder 273)
  - Mozart Divertimento #15: Adagio. Parts., [n.d.], (13 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 274)
  - Mozart Andante from Surprise Symphonie. Parts., Carl Fischer: New York, 1891, (26 parts) (Box 30, Folder 275)
  - Mozart "Adagio nom G minor Quintet." Parts., [n.d.], (8 pages bd. fair copy, 18 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 276)
  - Mozart Fantaisie in C Minor. Parts, [n.d.], (30 parts) (Box 30, Folder 277)
  - Mozart "Marcia alla Turca." Score and parts., 4 July 1891, (12 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 12 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 278)
  - Mozart Zauberflote Finale. Parts., [n.d.], (25 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 279)
  - Mozart "Belmont and Constance." Parts., [n.d.], (33 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 30, Folder 280)
  - Mozart Titus Overture. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (11 pages bd., 59 parts bd.) (Box 31, Folder 281)
    [With handwritten notes. Housed in four folders.]
  - Mozart Symphony K. 551 in C major. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (33 parts ) (Box 31, Folder 282)
  - Moszkowski, Moritz Fackeltanz, Opus 51. Parts., C.F. Peters: Leipzig, [n.d.], (43 parts) (Box 31, Folder 283)
  - Olsen, Ole "Suite fur Streichorchester." Parts., [n.d.], (23 parts) (Box 31, Folder 284)
  - Paderewski, I.J. Menuet. Parts., Carl Fischer: New York, [n.d.], (41 parts) (Box 31, Folder 285)
  - Pizzi, Emilio "Coquetterie" for strings. Scores (2) and parts. Cocks& Co.: London, 1894, (6 pages bd., 7 pages bd., 28 parts ) (Box 31, Folder 286)
  - Raff, Joachim Symphonie No. 4. Parts., Schuberth & Co.: Leipzig, [n.d.], (35 parts) (Box 31, Folder 287)
  - Rimsky-Korsakoff, Nikolaus Andreus Overture on Russian Themes. Parts., 1880, (46 parts) (Box 31, Folder 288)
  - Rimsky-Korsakoff, Nikolaus Andreus "La Grande Pague Russe." Parts., [n.d.], (38 parts) (Box 31, Folder 289)
  - Rimsky-Korsakoff, Nikolaus Andreus "Capriccio espagnol." Parts. [n.d.], (45 parts) (Box 31, Folder 290)
  - Gounod "Thanks Be to God" (Elijah). Parts., Witmark: New York, [n.d.], (24 a.ms. fair copy, 2 parts) (Box 32, Folder 291)
  - Gounod "Marche Religieuse." Score and parts., Leon Grus: Paris, [n.d.], (29 pages bd., 13 a.ms. fair copy, 18 parts) (Box 32, Folder 292)
  - Grieg, Edvard Norwegian Dances, op. 35 Parts., Peters: Leipzig, [n.d.], (71 pages bd., 41 parts) (Box 32, Folder 293)
  - Grieg, Edvard Peer Gynt, Suite No. 2, Opus 55. Parts., [n.d.], (50 parts) (Box 32, Folder 294)
  - Grieg, Edvard Orchestersuite, opus 46. Parts., [n.d.], (39 parts) (Box 32, Folder 295)
  - Donizetti "Les Martyrs" Overture. Score and parts., Tams: New York, [n.d.], (45 pages bd., 33 parts, 8 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 32, Folder 296)
    [1 of 2 sets. ]
  - Donizetti "Les Martyrs" Overture. Parts, Tams: New York, 22 July 1893, (26 parts, 10 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 32, Folder 297)
    [2 of 2 se ts.]
  - Beethoven, Ludwig von Symphony No. 6, op. 68. Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, (21 parts) (Box 32, Folder 298)
  - Brahms, Johannes Akademische Fest-Ouverture. Score and parts., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (, 81 parts, 3 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 32, Folder 299)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Octet, op. 166. Parts., [n.d.], (21 parts) (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Symphony No. 7 in C. "The Great." Parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (14 parts) (Box 33, Folder 301)
    [Number count uncertain as deteriorated scores are in disarray.]
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Zwei Satze" Symphony. Parts., Spina: Wein, [n.d.], (39 parts) (Box 33, Folder 302)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Moment Musical." Score and parts. [n.d.], (8 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 40 pages a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 303)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Fier-a-bras" Overture. Score and parts., Richault: Paris, [n.d.], (48 pages bd., 32 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 304)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Reitermarsch. Parts. Furstner: Berlin, [n.d.], (47 parts, 5 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 305)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Rosamunde" Overture. Parts., Fischer: New York, [n.d.], (29 parts) (Box 33, Folder 306)
  - Saint-Saens, C. "Ballet: Henry VIII." Score and parts., [n.d.], (101 pages bd., 41 parts, 1 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 307)
  - Rubenstein "Kamennoi-Ostrow" Nocturno. Parts., [n.d.], (46 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 308)
  - Rossini Semiramide Overture. Parts., Aibl: Munich, [n.d], (37 parts) (Box 33, Folder 309)
  - Rubenstein "Kammenoi-Ostrow." Score and parts. [n.d.], (20 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 35 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 310)
  - Rossini "Seige of Corinth." Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (35 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 311)
  - Rossini "Le Rendevouz." Score and parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (12 pages a.ms. fair copy, 35 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 312)
  - Rossini William Tell Overture. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (14 parts, 4 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 33, Folder 313)
  - Rudorff, Ernst "Otto der Schutz" Overture. Op. 12. Score and parts for orchestra., Seitz: Leipzig, [n.d.], (71 pages bd., 45 parts) (Box 33, Folder 314)
  - Schreiner, A. "Musikalische Tauschungen." Parts for orchestra., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (32 parts) (Box 34, Folder 315)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Marsch." Parts for orchestra., Furstner: Berlin, 11 June 1870, (41 parts) (Box 34, Folder 316)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Grand Marsch No. 409. Parts for orchestra, Oertel: Hannover, [n.d.], (38 parts) (Box 34, Folder 317)
    [First violin parts contain notes on direction.]
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Marche Militaire. Op. 57. Score and aparts for orchestra., [n.d.], (13 pages a.ms. fair copy, 35 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 34, Folder 318)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Symphonie. Parts for orchestra, Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (34 parts) (Box 34, Folder 319)
    [Identified as No. 7, No. 9, and D. 944 C major. Housed in two folders.]
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) "Thema mit Variationen (Die Forelle)." Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (27 parts) (Box 34, Folder 320)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Duo. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (36 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 34, Folder 321)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Symphony in D. 417, C minor. Score and parts for orchestra. Peters: Leipzig, [n.d.], (16 pages bd., 31 parts) (Box 34, Folder 322)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Tragische Symphonie No. 4. Part for Violin II., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (13 pages bd.) (Box 34, Folder 323)
    [Solitary part.]
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Ballet und Rosamonde. Parts for orchestra. [n.d.], (3 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 34, Folder 324)
    [Parts for Trumpet, Trombone basso, and Tromba.]
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Octet, Opus 166. Score. Peters: Leipzig and Berlin, [n.d.], (67 pages bd.) (Box 34, Folder 325)
    [With handwritten notes. No orchestral parts.]
  - Schuetz, Ernst Grand Waltz: "On the Wings of Song." Parts for orchestra., Kunkel Bros.: St. Louis, [n.d.], (9 parts) (Box 34, Folder 326)
    [Published version "To the Ladies of St. Paul."]
  - Schumann, Robert Geneva Overture. Op. 81. Parts for orchestra., Peters: Leipzig, [n.d.], (34 parts) (Box 34, Folder 327)
  - Schumann, Robert Overture Scherzo Finale. Score and parts for orchestra., Kistner: Leipzig, [n.d.], (126 pages bd., 37 parts) (Box 34, Folder 328)
  - Schumann, Robert Overture to Manfred. Score and parts for orchestra., Peters and Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (33 pages bd., 44[47] parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - Schumann, Robert Gerschwindmarsch. Parts for orchestra., Furstner: Berlin, [n.d.], (35 parts) (Box 35, Folder 330)
  - Schumann, Robert "Chant du Soir." Score and parts for strings., Durand, Schoenewerk & Co.: Paris, [n.d.], (2 pages bd., 25 parts a.ms. fair copy, 4 parts) (Box 35, Folder 331)
  - Schumann, Robert Symphony No. 4. Parts for orchestra., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (40 parts) (Box 35, Folder 332)
  - Schumann Symphony No. 3. Parts for orchestra. Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (35 parts, 3 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 35, Folder 333)
  - Schumann Symphony No. 2. Parts for orchestra., Whistling: Leipzig, [n.d.], (31 parts ) (Box 35, Folder 334)
  - Schumann Schlummerlied. Score and parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (8 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 29 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 35, Folder 335)
  - Schumann Bilder aus Osten, Opus 66. Parts for orchestra., Kistner: Leipzig, [n.d.], (38 parts) (Box 35, Folder 336)
  - Schumann "Stuck im Volkston." Score., Luckhardt: Berlin and Leipzig, [n.d.], (5 pages bd.) (Box 35, Folder 337)
  - Mozart Symphony No. 2. Part for Violin I., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig., [n.d.], (2 parts) (Box 35, Folder 338)
    [Second part incomplete.]
  - Brahms, Johannes Dritte Symphonie, Op. 90. Part for string bass., [n.d.], (1 page) (Box 35, Folder 339)
  - Smetana Richard III. Score and parts for orchestra. Simrock: Berlin, c. 1896, (37 parts, 75 pages bd.9) (Box 35, Folder 340)
  - Smetana Bartered Bride Overture. Score and parts for orchestra. Bote & Bock: Berlin, c. 11 June 1870, (37 pages bd., 37 parts) (Box 35, Folder 341)
  - Smetana Vysehrad. Parts for orchestra. [n.d.], (48 parts) (Box 35, Folder 342)
  - Smetana Symphony No. 1, op. 38. Parts for orchestra., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (36 parts, 2 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 35, Folder 343)
  - Smetana Vlatava Symphony. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (49 parts) (Box 36, Folder 344)
  - Smetana "Wallenstein's Lager.", Simrock: Berlin, c. 1896, (93 pages bd.) (Box 36, Folder 345)
    [Page 93 added in copyists's hand.]
  - Stix, Carl Trauergeister. Score and parts for orchestra., Offenbach: Mainx, c. 1894, (8 pages bd., 8 parts, 9 parts a.ms. fair copy, 1 cover a.ms.) (Box 36, Folder 346)
  - Strauss, Johann "Blue Danube" Waltz. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (33 parts) (Box 36, Folder 347)
  - Strauss, Johann Ninetta Waltz. Parts for orchestra. Cranz: Hamburg, [n.d.], (34 parts) (Box 36, Folder 348)
  - Strauss, Johann "Ritter Pasman": Ballet Music. Parts for orchestra., Simrock: Berlin, c. 11 June 1870, (35 parts) (Box 36, Folder 349)
  - Strauss, Johann "Ritter Pasman": Ballet Suite. Piano score and parts for orchestra., Leipzig, (36 parts) (Box 36, Folder 350)
  - Strauss, Johann Wiener Blut - Waltz. Parts for orchestra., Buttner: St. Petersburg, c. 1855, (35 parts) (Box 36, Folder 351)
  - Strauss, Johann Rathausball-Tanze. Parts for orchestra., Boise: New York, c. 1890, (36 parts) (Box 36, Folder 352)
  - Strauss, Johann "Wine, Women and Song" Waltz. Parts for orchestra. Buttner: St. Petersburg, [n.d.], (34 parts) (Box 36, Folder 353)
  - Strauss, Johann "Artist's Life" Waltz. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (33 parts) (Box 36, Folder 354)
  - Strauss, Johann "Gross-Wein" Waltz. Parts for orchestra., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (40 parts, 1 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 36, Folder 355)
  - Strauss, Johann "Du und du" Waltz. Parts for orchestra., Wein, [n.d.], (35 parts) (Box 36, Folder 356)
  - Strauss, Johann Nachtfalter Waltz. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (30 parts) (Box 36, Folder 357)
  - Strauss, Johann "Neu-Wein" Waltz. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (40 parts) (Box 36, Folder 358)
  - Strauss, Johann "Don Juan." Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (29 parts, 32 pages photocopies) (Box 36, Folder 359)
  - Sudessi, P. Gavotte. Parts for orchestra., Roder: Leipzig, c. 1894, (27 parts) (Box 36, Folder 360)
  - Tschaikovsky Capriccio Italien. Opus 45. Parts for orchestra., Rahter: Hamburg, [n.d.], (44 parts) (Box 36, Folder 361)
  - Tchaikovsky Casse-noisette. Suite. Opus 71. Parts for orchestra., Jurgenson: Moscow, [n.d.], (42 parts) (Box 37, Folder 362)
  - Tchaikovsky Suite No. 3. Opus 55. Parts for orchestra. Jurgenson: Moscow, [n.d.], (42 parts) (Box 37, Folder 363)
  - Tchaikovsky "Marche Solennelle." Parts for orchestra., Jurgenson: Moscow, [n.d.], (41 parts) (Box 37, Folder 364)
  - Tchaikovsky Marche Miniature. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (19 parts, 1 part a.ms. fair copy) (Box 37, Folder 365)
  - Tchaikovsky "Mazeppa" Dance Cosaque. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (46 parts) (Box 37, Folder 366)
  - Tchaikovsky "Marche Slave," Opus 31. Score and parts., [n.d.], (44 parts) (Box 37, Folder 367)
  - Tchaikovsky Suite No. 3. Part for violincello., [n.d.], (18 pages, 36 pages photocopies) (Box 37, Folder 368)
    [With handwritten notes. See also Seidl file 363.]
  - Tchaikovsky "La belle au bois dormant" No. 6. Opus 66. Parts for orchestra., Jurgenson: Moscow, [n.d.], (46 parts, 1 part a.ms.) (Box 37, Folder 369)
  - Tchaikovsky "Eugene Onegin, No. 13. Parts for orchestra., [n.d.], (25 parts, 11 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 37, Folder 370)
  - Vierling, Georg "Die Hermannsschlacht." Opus 31. Score., Breitkopf & Hartel: Leipzig, [n.d.], (92 pages bd.) (Box 37, Folder 371)
  - Vierling, Georg "Im Fruhling" Overture. Opus 24. Score. Stich & Druck: Leipzig, [n.d.], (51 pages bd.) (Box 37, Folder 372)